funny-games.biz 2019-03-18

# Funny-Games.biz Privacy Policy

I have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate funny-games.biz commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Any personal information that you provide to funny-games.biz shall stay absolutely safe, private and secure. I DO NOT share or resell personal information to outside sources.

INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED  
Funny-games.biz DO NOT log any information about you, your computer, your internet service provider or your internet connection.

COOKIES  
Funny-games.biz DO NOT use cookies to store information about your visits. However, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, Google advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING  
Funny-games.biz works with Google AdSense that serve ads to this site. Google AdWords may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information please see the [Google Privacy Policy Statement](https://www.google.com/privacy.html)

EXTERNAL LINKS  
Funny-games.biz contains links to other sites. I am not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

CONTACTING FUNNY GAMES  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can contact me.
